tenorshare.com 2019-12-22

# Tenorshare Co., Ltd. -Privacy

## Privacy Policy

Tenorshare Technology and its affiliates (" **Tenorshare** ") are committed to respecting and safeguarding the privacy of the personal information we gather. Please read the following Privacy Policy (this " **Policy** ") carefully to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it and what we do with it.

This Policy applies to personal information collected by all Tenorshare websites, products and services.

## What Personal Information Do We Collect

You may be asked to provide your personal information when placing an order on our websites or contacting customer services. This information includes your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number and credit card expiration date. In many cases, we will need these to complete the transaction, help provide a better support and respond to any queries.

We may share your information with trusted third parties who adhere to Tenorshare’s commitment to protect your privacy. To comply with applicable laws or respond to valid legal procedures, we may also disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government agencies.

## How Do We Use Your Personal Information

We may use your personal information to:

  * Verify your identification to complete an order or provide appropriate services.
  * Respond to any requires and offer technical support.
  * Keep you posted on Tenorshare’s latest products, software updates, prize promotion and after-sales services. You can always choose to stop receiving from us if not willing to be on our mailing list.

## How Do We Save and Protect Your Personal Information

Your privacy is important to Tenorshare. We use appropriate physical, management, and technical measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use, modification, damage, or loss. Tenorshare will not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. Tenorshare will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever.

## Disclosure of Your Personal Information

At times Tenorshare may make certain personal information available to third-party credit card processors to fulfill customer orders and deliver products.

Tenorshare uses secure server hosted by MyCommerce, Share-it and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information before it is sent to us, including name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, etc. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition.

## MyCommerce

MyCommerce offers a self-service SaaS ecommerce platform to support software sales for B2B or B2C with nearly 25 years of industry experiences. Tenorshare uses MyCommerce to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase. Check [Privacy Policy of MyCommerce](https://cs.mycommerce.com/privacy-policy/mycommerce/mcie/en_US).

## Share-it

Share-it offers easy and quick solution to sell software and digital products online globally. Check [Privacy Policy of Share-it](https://secure.tenorshare.com/info/privacy_statement).

## About Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that a website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our website and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

Using cookies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our websites people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.

## Updates

Tenorshare reserves the right to update or change this Policy at any time. Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you via different channels, such as by posting a notice on our websites or by providing a notice directly to you.

For any questions, please enter our Customer Service Center for help. Thank you.
